# JAKUB CHOJNA

As an architect and 3d graphic artist I developed a strong sense of aesthetics and visual composition. I have a background in programming parametric architecture. For one year I have been learning frontend development on my own and I am fully decided to develop myself in this area. In particular, I am very keen to learn more about technologies oriented around programming side of frontend development and creative coding, including React, Redux, GraphQl, server-side rendering, CSS-in-JS, data visualization, WebGL

# **PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE**

## 2008 - Present Freelance 3d Graphic Artist

Self employed | Remote

- created photorealistic architectural visualizations of interiors and exteriors in 3ds Max, V-Ray and Photoshop
- worked for clients such as: Echo Development, Terroir, Konior Studio, Studio Thörnblom, Real2B Development, Mallson, MOFO Architekci

#### 2017 - 2018 **Freelance Architect**

Self employed | Remote

created series of furniture prototypes developed refurbishment project of single-family house in Lublin in collaboration with architect Piotr Gniewek

#### 01 - 06.2018 **Svet Vmes**

Architect | 3d Visualizer | Ljubljana, Slovenia

- prepared in team work preliminary project concepts, scheme design and construction drawings in AutoCad
- created 3d models, 2d graphics and photorealistic visualizations for the purpose of design process and final presentations for clients

#### 2015 - 2017 Mofo Architekci

Architect | 3d Visualizer | Warsaw

prepared preliminary project concepts, schematic drawings, façade design proposals and virtual 3d models of the buildings for commercial use and professional presentations

#### 2011 - 2013 Activum Projektowanie

Architect | Intern | Warsaw

participated in concept, schematic and design development phases of residential interiors, small multi-family house, retail building, renovations and expansions as well as furniture design and competitions

#### 2010 - 2013 **Euro Info Group**

3d Software Tutor | Warsaw

- carried out several courses on 3dsMax and V-ray at the basic level
- the course program consisted of 3d modeling, texturing and mapping, lightning, rendering, post-production of architectural rendering and the very basis of animation and particle systems

# **EDUCATION**

2011 - 2014 Warsaw University of Technology

Faculty of Architecture | Master's Degree

2006 - 2010 Warsaw University of Technology

Faculty of Architecture | Bachelor's Degree

I hereby consent to processing by the advertiser of my personal data, included in my application documents, for the purposes to implement the recruitment process according to the act of 29 August 1997 on personal data protection (consolidated text: Journal of Laws of 2016, pos. 922). I also consent to processing of my personal data by the advertiser for the purposes of any future recruitment processes.



+48 519 816 323

frontend@jakubchojna.pl

frontend.jakubchojna.pl/

### **WORKING KNOWLEDGE**







**HTML** 

**CSS** 



**FIGMA** 



**VS CODE** 

**LANGUAGES** 

**English:** advanced

**German:** elementary

Polish: native

### **INTERESTS**

- road cycling
- photography
- string art